<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<anime_list>
  <report_date>2026-06-21</report_date>
  <anime>
    <title>Sousou no Frieren</title>
    <score>9.26</score>
    <episodes>28</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1015/138006.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>During their decade-long quest to defeat the Demon King, the members of the hero's party—Himmel himself, the priest Heiter, the dwarf warrior Eisen, and the elven mage Frieren—forge bonds through adventures and battles, creating unforgettable precious memories for most of them.

However, the time that Frieren spends with her comrades is equivalent to merely a fraction of her life, which has lasted over a thousand years. When the party disbands after their victory, Frieren casually returns to her "usual" routine of collecting spells across the continent. Due to her different sense of time, she seemingly holds no strong feelings toward the experiences she went through.

As the years pass, Frieren gradually realizes how her days in the hero's party truly impacted her. Witnessing the deaths of two of her former companions, Frieren begins to regret having taken their presence for granted; she vows to better understand humans and create real personal connections. Although the story of that once memorable journey has long ended, a new tale is about to begin.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu 4th Season</title>
    <score>9.19</score>
    <episodes>19</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1540/155824.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>In the deadly battle at the Watergate City of Priestella, Subaru and his allies barely emerged victorious—but their triumph came at a great cost. Through the "Authority of Gluttony," Rem was put into suspended animation, while Crusch's memories and even Julius’s name were devoured. As he searches for a way to save them, Subaru learns of the "Sage" Shaula—an all-seeing being said to possess every form of knowledge. His next destination is the Pleiades Watchtower, home to the Sage, the farthest tower standing in the vast, uncharted desert known as the Auguria Dunes—a place so perilous that even the mightiest "Sword Saint," Reinhard, failed to conquer it. The fury of nature, unknown magical beasts, and unimaginable dangers lie ahead. Together with his friends, Subaru embarks on a life-risking journey to reclaim what was lost.

(Source: Kadokawa, edited)</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Steel Ball Run: JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken</title>
    <score>9.11</score>
    <episodes>N/A</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1448/154111.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>In the American Old West, the world's greatest race is about to begin. Thousands line up in San Diego to travel over six thousand kilometers for a chance to win the grand prize of fifty million dollars. With the era of the horse reaching its end, contestants are allowed to use any kind of vehicle they wish. Competitors will have to endure grueling conditions, traveling up to a hundred kilometers a day through uncharted wastelands. The Steel Ball Run is truly a one-of-a-kind event.

The youthful Johnny Joestar, a crippled former horse racer, has come to San Diego to watch the start of the race. There he encounters Gyro Zeppeli, a racer with two steel balls at his waist instead of a gun. Johnny witnesses Gyro using one of his steel balls to unleash a fantastical power, compelling a man to fire his gun at himself during a duel. In the midst of the action, Johnny happens to touch the steel ball and feels a power surging through his legs, allowing him to stand up for the first time in two years. Vowing to find the secret of the steel balls, Johnny decides to compete in the race, and so begins his bizarre adventure across America on the Steel Ball Run.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood</title>
    <score>9.11</score>
    <episodes>64</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1208/94745.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>After a horrific alchemy experiment goes wrong in the Elric household, brothers Edward and Alphonse are left in a catastrophic new reality. Ignoring the alchemical principle banning human transmutation, the boys attempted to bring their recently deceased mother back to life. Instead, they suffered brutal personal loss: Alphonse's body disintegrated while Edward lost a leg and then sacrificed an arm to keep Alphonse's soul in the physical realm by binding it to a hulking suit of armor.

The brothers are rescued by their neighbor Pinako Rockbell and her granddaughter Winry. Known as a bio-mechanical engineering prodigy, Winry creates prosthetic limbs for Edward by utilizing "automail," a tough, versatile metal used in robots and combat armor. After years of training, the Elric brothers set off on a quest to restore their bodies by locating the Philosopher's Stone—a powerful gem that allows an alchemist to defy the traditional laws of Equivalent Exchange.

As Edward becomes an infamous alchemist and gains the nickname "Fullmetal," the boys' journey embroils them in a growing conspiracy that threatens the fate of the world.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Chainsaw Man Movie: Reze-hen</title>
    <score>9.07</score>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1763/150638.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>Despite the immediate challenges following becoming a devil hunter with the Public Safety Bureau, Denji has quickly adapted to his new life and responsibilities. As the chaos of Denji's first ordeal with Public Safety settles down, the elite devil hunter Makima decides to take Denji out on a date. Although the date strengthens his affection for Makima and he swears to not fall in love with anyone else, Denji soon finds himself in a tricky situation when he meets a seemingly innocent cafe worker named Reze.

With her forward and flirty demeanor, Reze immediately captures Denji's heart, driving him to frequent the cafe where she works and deepen his relationship with her. However, Denji is completely oblivious to the fact that meeting Reze might have grave consequences beyond simply deciding which woman his heart belongs to. 

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Steins;Gate</title>
    <score>9.07</score>
    <episodes>24</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1935/127974.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>Eccentric scientist Rintarou Okabe has a never-ending thirst for scientific exploration. Together with his ditzy but well-meaning friend Mayuri Shiina and his roommate Itaru Hashida, Okabe founds the Future Gadget Laboratory in the hopes of creating technological innovations that baffle the human psyche. Despite claims of grandeur, the only notable "gadget" the trio have created is a microwave that has the mystifying power to turn bananas into green goo.

However, when Okabe attends a conference on time travel, he experiences a series of strange events that lead him to believe that there is more to the "Phone Microwave" gadget than meets the eye. Apparently able to send text messages into the past using the microwave, Okabe dabbles further with the "time machine," attracting the ire and attention of the mysterious organization SERN.

Due to the novel discovery, Okabe and his friends find themselves in an ever-present danger. As he works to mitigate the damage his invention has caused to the timeline, Okabe fights a battle to not only save his loved ones but also to preserve his degrading sanity.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3 Part 2</title>
    <score>9.05</score>
    <episodes>10</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1517/100633.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>Seeking to restore humanity's diminishing hope, the Survey Corps embark on a mission to retake Wall Maria, where the battle against the merciless "Titans" takes the stage once again.

Returning to the tattered Shiganshina District that was once his home, Eren Yeager and the Corps find the town oddly unoccupied by Titans. Even after the outer gate is plugged, they strangely encounter no opposition. The mission progresses smoothly until Armin Arlert, highly suspicious of the enemy's absence, discovers distressing signs of a potential scheme against them. 

Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3 Part 2 follows Eren as he vows to take back everything that was once his. Alongside him, the Survey Corps strive—through countless sacrifices—to carve a path towards victory and uncover the secrets locked away in the Yeager family's basement.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Gintama°</title>
    <score>9.05</score>
    <episodes>51</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/72078.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>Gintoki, Shinpachi, and Kagura return as the fun-loving but broke members of the Yorozuya team! Living in an alternate-reality Edo, where swords are prohibited and alien overlords have conquered Japan, they try to thrive on doing whatever work they can get their hands on. However, Shinpachi and Kagura still haven't been paid... Does Gin-chan really spend all that cash playing pachinko?

Meanwhile, when Gintoki drunkenly staggers home one night, an alien spaceship crashes nearby. A fatally injured crew member emerges from the ship and gives Gintoki a strange, clock-shaped device, warning him that it is incredibly powerful and must be safeguarded. Mistaking it for his alarm clock, Gintoki proceeds to smash the device the next morning and suddenly discovers that the world outside his apartment has come to a standstill. With Kagura and Shinpachi at his side, he sets off to get the device fixed; though, as usual, nothing is ever that simple for the Yorozuya team.

Filled with tongue-in-cheek humor and moments of heartfelt emotion, Gintama's fourth season finds Gintoki and his friends facing both their most hilarious misadventures and most dangerous crises yet.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Gintama: The Final</title>
    <score>9.05</score>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1245/116760.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>Two years have passed following the Tendoshuu's invasion of the O-Edo Central Terminal. Since then, the Yorozuya have gone their separate ways. Foreseeing Utsuro's return, Gintoki Sakata begins surveying Earth's ley lines for traces of the other man's Altana. After an encounter with the remnants of the Tendoshuu—who continue to press on in search of immortality—Gintoki returns to Edo.

Later, the regrouped Shinsengumi and Yorozuya begin an attack on the occupied Central Terminal. With the Altana harvested by the wreckage of the Tendoshuu's ship in danger of detonating, the Yorozuya and their allies fight their enemies while the safety of Edo—and the rest of the world—hangs in the balance. Fulfilling the wishes of their teacher, Shouyou Yoshida's former students unite and relive their pasts one final time in an attempt to save their futures.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
  <anime>
    <title>Hunter x Hunter (2011)</title>
    <score>9.03</score>
    <episodes>148</episodes>
    <image>https://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1337/99013.jpg</image>
    <synopsis>Hunters devote themselves to accomplishing hazardous tasks, all from traversing the world's uncharted territories to locating rare items and monsters. Before becoming a Hunter, one must pass the Hunter Examination—a high-risk selection process in which most applicants end up handicapped or worse, deceased.

Ambitious participants who challenge the notorious exam carry their own reason. What drives 12-year-old Gon Freecss is finding Ging, his father and a Hunter himself. Believing that he will meet his father by becoming a Hunter, Gon takes the first step to walk the same path.

During the Hunter Examination, Gon befriends the medical student Leorio Paladiknight, the vindictive Kurapika, and ex-assassin Killua Zoldyck. While their motives vastly differ from each other, they band together for a common goal and begin to venture into a perilous world.

[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
  </anime>
</anime_list>
